chillivanilla.com 2012-10-14

# Promotional Codes, Voucher Codes & Discount vouchers

**Updated: 31/05/2009**

**Information sharing**   
Tanner Ross & Co Limited ("We"), the owner and operator of HotVouchers.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all personal information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement. 

**Third Parties**   
We may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month but does not contain behavioural or identifying information about any individual member. 

**Obtaining your consent**   
By using the HotVouchers.com web site, you give Tanner Ross & Co Limited permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. 

**Cookies**   
Upon your visit to HotVouchers.com, a cookie may be sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access parts of the HotVouchers.com site. 

**Direct Mailings**   
If you register with HotVouchers.com for our newsletters we will send you information about our voucher codes, deals, or other products and services we feel may interest you. Your e-mail address may also be used to send you information about our other websites that we feel are relevant to your registration on HotVouchers.com. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

**Links**   
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by HotVouchers.com are not under the control of Tanner Ross & Co Limited and as such have their own privacy policies. We can not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

**Policy Maintenance**   
HotVouchers.com may occasionally amend the policy contained upon this page. We therefore suggest you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time. 

Questions, comments and requests for information related to this privacy policy are welcomed. Our contact details can be obtained from the foot of this page.
